Allen, what did
you just tear up?
Oh, Grandpa,
it's just a painting.
These guys were
trying to give it
to you as a gift.
But I couldn't tell
you it was so fake,
I just tore it up.
A fake painting?
They said
the painting
was a Picasso, worth
three million dollars.
But I mean,
look at them.
They could not afford
something like that.
It has to be a fake.
Picasso...
Oh my God.
See?
Grandpa doesn't
even want
that kind of trash
messing
up the floor.
You guys better
get out of here.
You're not welcome.
Allen?
Come here.
Yes, Grandpa.
Closer.
Yeah.
That's my boy,
that's my boy.
All that
college education.
And you turned
out to be
such a big idiot!
Just shut
your mouth!
Why did
you hit me?
You just destroyed
three million dollars,
you idiot!
Three million dollars?
You can't believe
their stories.
-I have been
-Obviously a knockoff.
collecting and
it takes longer
than you've been alive
and I know
real from fake.
It was worth more
than three million
until you ruined it!
What? It's real?